MICHAEL IVANOV

Junior Front-end Developer

22/12/1994

4 +380932067980

■ loadszz94@gmail.com

@Loadszz

in linkedin.com

github.com/Loadszz

About

"I'm a 28 years old a developer with experience building websites. I have experience with HTML and CSS 3, JavaScript, jQuery, React, SEO.

I'm open for constructive criticism in the workflow. I'm highly motivated to gain new skills and experience so I looking for a strong team with big ambitions.

Work experience

10/2020 - Present

Front-end Developer, SEO

Part-time

10/2019 - Present

Front-end Developer

Part-time

Freelance

Education

11/2020 - 02/2021

Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

IT school — Lemon

09/2020 – 31/2021 KHARKIV, UKRAINE

Master Degree

Program Subject Area "Information

Technologies"

Program Subject Area "Computer

Sciences"

Kharkiv National University of Civil Engineering and Architecture

09/2012 – 03/2018 KHARKIV, UKRAINE **Master Degree**

Program Subject Area "History and

archeology"

V.N. Karazin Kharkiv National

University

Skills

Front-End

✓ HTML, HTML5

✓ CSS, CSS3

✓ SASS/SCSS

✓ Flexbox

✓ Pixel perfect

✓ Basic JS

✓ Basic jQuery

✓ Basic React JS

√ Git

✓ Gulp

✓ Next JS

√ Tailwind CSS

Software

√ VS Code

√ Figma

✓ Adobe Photoshop

✓ Avocode

✓ Zeplin

Languages

Native **Ukrainian**

B1 English

Native Russian